<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FUGA POR MEXICO</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">User</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">sebas.rg07@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Favorites</string>
    <string name="menu_slideshow">Discounts of the day</string>
    <string name="menu_viajes">Mis Trips</string>
    <string name="menu_fotos">Photos</string>
    //
    <string name="texto1">Password</string>
    <string name="texto2">Email</string>
    <string name="texto3">Login</string>
    <string name="texto4">Register</string>
    <string name="texto5">User register</string>
    <string name="texto6">User</string>
    <string name="texto7">Already have an account?</string>
    //
    <string name="texto8">Explore Aguascalientes</string>
    <string name="texto9">Aguascalientes Events</string>
    <string name="texto10">Discover Aguascalientes</string>
    <string name="texto11">San Marcos Garden</string>
    <string name="texto12">Bullring</string>
    <string name="texto13">San Marcos Fair</string>
    <string name="texto14">Historic Center of Aguascalientes</string>
    <string name="texto15">Main Square</string>
    <string name="texto16">Aguascalientes Cathedral</string>
    <string name="texto17">Cerro del Muerto</string>
    <string name="texto18">Temple of San Antonio</string>
    <string name="texto19">Island San Marcos</string>
    <string name="texto20">Museum of Aguascalientes</string>
    <string name="texto21">Restaurants</string>
    <string name="texto22">Hotels</string>
    <string name="texto23">Pubs</string>
    <string name="texto24">Parking lot</string>
    <string name="texto25">Sign off</string>
    <string name="texto26">Delete account</string>
    //
    <string name="texto27">Telephone:</string>
    <string name="texto28">Horary:</string>
    <string name="texto29">Attention:</string>
    <string name="texto30">Tuesday/Sunday</string>
    <string name="texto31">Web</string>
    <string name="texto32">Call</string>
    <string name="texto33">All the days</string>
    <string name="texto34">Name:</string>
    <string name="texto35">Go</string>
    <string name="texto36">Promotions</string>
    <string name="texto37">Scan your codes</string>
    <string name="texto38">Scan</string>
    //
    <string name="texto40">The first Aguascalientes fair was held in 1828. In its beginnings it was held in the month of November, giving rise to the Parián located in front of the San Diego Temple, which had exclusively commercial purposes. It changed to the month of April, within the celebrations of San Marcos, an old Indian town located a few blocks from the main square of the capital
With the arrival of the railroad in 1884, the city strengthened its old vocation as merchants and, with it, its regional primacy, so that the fair could be promoted and known beyond the limits of a small town festival. Within the popular imagination, the coronation of the Queen (a tradition that began in the 1920s) represents not only a beauty contest but also the longing for a society, where the governor crowns the chosen one, the poet improvises the eulogy and the people admire the majesty of the act.</string>
    <string name="texto41">The Cerro del Muerto is a mountainous massif, which is located in the municipalities of Aguascalientes and Jesús María, in the State of Aguascalientes in Mexico, it presents an oak forest in the upper parts and in some slopes and ravines.</string>
    <string name="texto42">Calvillo Magical Town</string>
    <string name="texto43">It received its appointment as a Magic Town in November 2012. Located in the state of Aguascalientes, it bears the name of Calvillo, in honor of its benefactor. Its origin occurs with the establishment of a congregation of Nahua Indians of San José de Huejúcar, which means "place of willows."</string>
    <string name="texto44">Temple of San Antonio de Padua</string>
    <string name="texto45">The temple of San Antonio is a monument and religious masterpiece, located in the historic center of the City of Aguascalientes, in the state of the same name, designed and built by the self-taught practical architect Refugio Reyes Rivas. Its construction began in 1895 and the work was completed in 1908.</string>
    <string name="texto46">Any questions or comments can be sent to our email fugapormexico@gmail.com
Through this email you can obtain information or resolve any questions you have about the application, and thus be able to provide you with the necessary information.</string>
    <string name="texto47">Organization: Fuga Por México
Additional contacts:
Sebastian Gallegos Gallegos 17150056@aguascalientes.tecnm.mx
Fernanda Paulina razo rodriguez17150408@aguascalientes.tecnm.mx</string>
    <string name="texto48">A cordial greeting to all our users, we hope you are enjoying our app and it is helping you to find what you were looking for in our beautiful State of Aguascalientes.</string>

</resources>